{
    "subject": "resource/Romuald_the_Reindeer",
    "predicate": "ontology/voice",
    "object": "resource/Kenneth_Waller",
    "human_readable": "Romuald the Reindeer's voice is Kenneth Waller.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8726978898048401,
            "question": "Who voices Romuald the Reindeer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7464872002601624,
            "question": "Are there other characters voiced by Kenneth Waller?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7006546258926392,
            "question": "Where might we hear Romuald the Reindeer's voice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6030592322349548,
            "question": "What is Kenneth Waller known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5516802072525024,
            "question": "What kind of character is Romuald the Reindeer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49050816893577576,
            "question": "Is Romuald the Reindeer a fictional character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42746633291244507,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Kenneth Waller's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09967365115880966,
            "question": "What is the significance of voice acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05563737824559212,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by voice actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03611377254128456,
            "question": "How does voice acting contribute to storytelling?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Romuald the Reindeer's voice is Kenneth Waller.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5667_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges faced by voice actors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5667_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of voice acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5667_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Kenneth Waller's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5667_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5667_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5667_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5667_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5667_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5667_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5667_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5667_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5667_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5667_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5667_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided confirm that Kenneth Waller was indeed the voice of Romuald the Reindeer, as mentioned in multiple files (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5667/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5667/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt, and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5667/re-ranker-msmarco/123.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that \"His last role was a voiceover for the animated film 'Romuald the Reindeer'.\" and provide Kenneth Waller as the actor for the voice role in the Cast section, confirming that Kenneth Waller provided the voice for Romuald the Reindeer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}